It's my life, it's your life, fighting for
tomorrow. Go catch what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life, run
like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong, believe
you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going. I'll not stay.
Hey.
Let's do it again.
You know what I mean? Baby.
No one can make it.
My dream comes true.
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what it is.
Something is testing.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the crater.
No, there are no rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid with me.
Hit me, I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so.
Can you only wait out?
We can let go together.
Baby, grow with a rose.
It's my life. It's your life.
Fight if you don't want to
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can't achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life. It's your life.
Fight for your wife.
That I want, but you really want.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life. It's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of days.
You make my day every day.
Hello, knock-knock.
Can Sabo please come out to play?
I heard you.
You liar!
You were zoning out!
Your eyes have been glossed
over this whole time!
Also, remember you have a position now.
You can't go picking fights with Navy
admirals over personal grudges, okay?
You're going to lead our
army into an Alto war.
But my brother comes first, always.
Huh?
Sabo! What?
Your reckless behavior is going
to cause problems for me, too.
Boo-hoo! Sabo!
I learned through new info.
When all is said and done, the Navy and
Doflamingo are both unnecessary here.
We're birds of a feather, if you will.
The Navy and I can never play
the hero for this kingdom.
It's simply not our place.
What if someone catches
on to your rationale?
They won't.
All they'll see is that I
hit a snag getting past you.
Said like a true gambler.
Lady Luck's on my side.
Kay, understood, you got it?
Huh?
Zappo, the nerve!
I'm getting really tired of
being chewed out on your behalf.
That hurt.
We'll lure the other criminals out
with the ones we already caught.
It'll be foolproof.
I'm sorry! I really am! Somebody help me!
He's got a knife!
Oh, we are free!
What about the berries?
I thought you guys came here to catch us.
This okay?
We messed up.
We were wrong from the get-go.
We've had a decade-long
grudge against King Rick,
but how could we do this to him
when he's a victim of Doflamingo II?
I can't believe we
praised that evil pirate.
And even after we learned the truth.
about what he did to our loved ones?
and how he enslaved them.
We were still seeking salvation
from that deceitful bastard.
We're all so confused.
We still don't know what
we're supposed to do.
What's gonna happen to us?
Please save us.
King Rick!
What in the heck?
A change of heart, I presume?
They have taken me.
King Rick, please tell
us what we should do.
If you propose we fight,
we shall take aboard.
Please, King Rick.
We await your command.
Please, please, King.
Hmm.
In that event, I say we stay put.
Why's that?
If it's necessary, we can brace
ourselves for death later.
Without realizing it, it seems that I've
come to believe in Luffy's victory as well.
Historically, Dressrosa has
stood as a symbol of peace.
I'll be damned if I see this
kingdom fall into war again.
Why is he here?
We can't catch a break!
King Rick, sir.
It seems like we're both about to
go all in on this high-stakes game.
One for Straw Hat.
How do you like that, huh?
I'll admit that was quite a blow. You see?
I told you it wouldn't kill him.
Now we've wasted our only
chance to use that trick.
Stop sending fakes! Fight me!
Hey, we know all about how
your ability operates, Law.
You must have forgotten
that we had our eyes
on the app-op room for
quite some time now.
You can chop me up into a million pieces,
but I'm gonna turn back to normal.
Now I'm ready for round two.
You finally noticed the radio knife doesn't
work the same as my regular amputation.
For the next few minutes, you'll
be unable to use your ability.
You might as well relax,
you're not going anywhere!
Seriously?
Trouble's in trouble!
My nose is running!
Come on, wait!
At least get me a tissue!
Damn it, you!
No!
Roof!
Stop your crystal trainer!
Don't you dare come near me!
Injection!
Snap-like answer! It's me!
Shots!
And the finisher!
Fulbright!
Trophy!
Do you recall what I hate more than
anything else in the world, Law?
It's being looked down on! Remember!
Don't you dare!
I can't stop.
I don't want to hurt you.
You've got to dodge me.
No! No!
Dammit, Straw Hats!
Knowing what I'm capable of,
did you really believe me?
You could beat me.
The fact that you wretched little
brats thought I was so weak
that I would fall to you in your
pathetic surprise attack—well,
I find that to be the highest
form of disrespect imaginable!
You're so screwed.
Let me tell you:
I descend from the noblest
of bloodlines in the world.
The celestial
dragons—just the fact that
I exist makes me deserving of admiration.
I possessed
the rarest of powers
known to man; however,
my worthless father abandoned
the greatest birthright in the
world—our priceless divine
nobility—then our fate was sealed.
our fate was sealed
My whole family was sentenced to suffer
among the commoners in this rotten cesspool.
Live like a human, he would squawk.
Well, screw that!
My father was nothing but an imbecile.
Hiya, Daddy!
Where did all the slaves go?
Hey, let's buy some more!
Oh, Daddy, why are they
not kneeling before me?
Daddy, why?
Everyone is coming after us!
They're a family of Celestial
Dragons! Don't kill them!
Let's make them suffer instead!
I experienced both heaven
and hell firsthand.
I took it upon myself
to end my suffering by
bringing the head of my own
father back to Marie Joie!
But,
can you believe that the
Celestial Dragons would tell
a ten-year-old boy they
wouldn't take back someone from
A line of traitors. It was
then that I found there was no
escaping this hell from that
moment forward i swore that
i would destroy everything
they held dear to put it
frankly every damn thing in
the world the lives you've led
cannot possibly be compared
to what i've been through i'm
not wasting my time screwing
around with brats like you
It's below me!
You don't have to do this!
Please, sir!
I want to stop!
I really don't want to do this!
Run!
I can't...
I can't control my body!
It's moving on its own!
Please!
Forgive me, I can't fight it!
With this much loot, we can
rebuild our ship, no problem!
at all.
Yeah, does she, does she? Damn it!
Stop right there!
We don't have time to deal
with your pillaging right now!
I can't escape!
It's gonna kill itself at this rate.
Drink it!
We still have some ammo, don't we?
Honestly,
what are you expecting of us?
We're short on both tranquilizers and men.
We've got our hands tied.
Vice Admiral Maynard!
What now?
Sir, status report.
It's concerning Sabo and Admiral Isho.
The fight between them ended in a draw.
Don't joke around.
How's that possible?
Our admirals from the
Navy headquarters are
some of the best combatants
we have to offer.
Why not Isho?
They're furious!
That's why the world government
has no business playing god.
Something's not adding up here.
What should we do?
There's no time for this.
I'll settle it later.
Right now we have to get
this chaos under control.
We can round up all pirates
who went after the flamingo.
Once the kingdom is safe,
do I make myself clear, sir?
Do not harm any civilians or animals.
Your orders are to sedate
anyone who is not in control.
Are you kids okay?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, God!
Octopus Stare!
Almost had me! Behind you!
You can't even comprehend
the situation, can you?
Let me put it this way.
If people could harm a celestial dragon,
just imagine the things they'd do.
Humanity is cruel.
Vicious by nature.
What are you talking
about, you fake mingo?
All right.
I think it's about time we start
rolling out those executions.
You're first on my list, Law.
Oh, hey!
One thing still doesn't make sense to me.
As a former Celestial Dragon,
banished from Arishua,
how do you still wield their power?
CP0 is working directly
under the world government.
But you called them here this morning.
That's your last request.
You really want to know the dirty details?
It's because I know all about a very
important national treasure—something
that's hidden within the holy land of
Marie Joie—it gives you
that much leverage, yes?
You could even say its very
existence could shake humanity.
Get him kill doflamingo?
That child must not be allowed
to see another day! To them,
I was a ticking time bomb—an escapee
with dirt that could destroy their world.
But those cowards became quite cooperative
once they realized they couldn't kill me,
though they did try—if only
I'd had the op—op fruit
in my possession at that
crucial point in time.
Things would have played
out a bit differently;
I would have been able to
utilize Marie Joie's...
able to utilize marie joie's
national treasure and seize
the world by the net that day.
That should show you just how valuable
your fruit actually is.
Aside from personality transplant
surgery, there's another use.
Are you
even aware of that fact law?
In the right hands,
the op-op fruit has the power to make
mankind's oldest most sought-after dream a
reality that's why
you'll hear many refer to
it as the ultimate devil
fruit yeah i know i've
no interest in using
it for that though the
great mystery of the fruit is its ability
known as the perpetual
youth surgery right it
grants eternal life and
yet By performing it,
the surgeon sacrifices
their own in exchange
Bingo!
That's why I had no
intention of letting you
eat it But you repaid my
kindness with betrayal.
Then allow me to apologize for that one.
Diamante's sword play.
Go, Bullet String.
And Lao G's martial arts. Rune!
An injection shot!
Oh, and that one's from Gladius.
You learned all your fighting skills from
us, yet you bite the hand that feeds you.
Yeah, so?
The only reason I'm alive
now is thanks to Karoo.
But I'm grateful to you, too.
You gave me the power I need
to kick your ass after all.
Wait, are you serious?
Stop laughing! I mean it!
You can't kill a person
with your spirit alone, boy.
I told you guys, I have explosives.
You shouldn't mess with pirates!
You can't catch me! Where's the captain?
Duffy's a very busy fellow and
doesn't have time for a brat like you.
Hmm, you kind of just had a weight to
us since you're gonna die soon anyway.
But, when though?
How long, huh?
When you get a crow, kiddo?
In three years and two months from now.
And who told you that?
I read it on my medical charts.
My dead father was a doctor.
What a smart little punk.
I want to use my last
three years killing as
many people as I can and
destroying everything.
Oh, wow, get a lot of Mr. Big Talk here.
I got sniffles.
Well, not all hope is lost
since we accept children.
I'd say we've had about 100
or so come through here.
But most of the little rugrats run
away crying within a day or two.
You think you have what
it takes, little guy?
Hey, guess what, Diamante?
Yeah, guess what, Treville?
See them?
That's Buffalo and Baby Five.
The only ones remaining.
Well, what do you want?
Cora's on his way here now!
He tripped! Yay! I knew it!
That is so Cora!
Bell on your butt!
Oh, jeez.
Hey, Okoda, I brought you a cup of tea.
It's real hot.
Corazon, did you finish the job?
Then hand over my cut.
We got to make sure there's transparency
when it comes to dealing with money.
Law, was it?
This guy who just came back
is an executive like us.
His name is Couran.
He may come across as
a thick-headed klutz,
but truth is, he comes
from a powerful bloodline.
That is to say he's
Dofie's little brother.
As a side note, he doesn't talk
anymore because of some old trauma.
Oh, right!
He hates kids, so watch out!
He's dead!
He threw that kid right
out with the trash!
What's wrong with him?
He must be nuts!
I'M GONNA KILL HIM!
GONNA CALL FIRE AGAIN!